Guide to the Cornell University Library records, [ca.1868]-2010.
Cornell University Library records
- Grant Files
  - Dean, J. Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project; Getty Grant Program, September 2001 - September 30, 2003 (Box 131)
    Getty L89-8508
  - Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project - Folder 1, April 24, 1998 - November 14, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 32)
  - Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project - Folder 2, June 1988- January 2003 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    The earliest dates are due to the presence of Gettry Grant Program guidelines.
  - Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project - Folder 3, 1998 - April 22, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project - Folder 4, November 9, 2000 - November 24, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Getty Post-Graduate Internship Project - Folder 5, January 11, 2001 - November 24, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Dean, J. Preservation and Digitization of Political Americana, October 1, 2001 - September 30, 2003 (Box 132)
    IMLS L89-8313
  - Preservation and Digitization of Political Americana, July 8, 1999 - January 31, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Stam, Deirdre State of Preservation Programs in American College and Research Libraries, October 2001 - September 2002 (Box 132)
    IMLS/CLIR
  - State of Preservation Programs in American College and Research Libraries - Folder 1, September 19, 2001 - October 10, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - State of Preservation Programs in American College and Research Libraries - Folder 2, September 11, 2001 - October 10, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Dean, J. Web Based Training Tutorials, October 1, 2001 - June 30, 2004 (Box 132)
    CLIR L89-8509; OSP 41172
  - Web Based Training Tutorials - CLIR (Contract), October 8, 2000 - August 11, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Web Based Training Tutorials, June 5, 2001 - August 9, 2004 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Riedy, Allen J. Images of Southeast Asia, December 1, 2001 - November 20, 2004 (Box 132)
    L81-8300; OSP 41907/A001
  - Images of Southeast Asia, February 2002 - January 2006 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Kenney, A. RLG Contract; L89-8505; OSP 32743; replaced w/L61-8501, January 1, 2002 - December 31, 2002 (Box 132)
    RLF
  - RLG Contract, March 27, 1997 - January 28, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Dean, J. Investigation of Hermetic Sealing as a Means of Extending the Life of Film-Based Material, August 1, 2002 - December 31, 2005 (Box 132)
    Ford Foundation L89-8510; OSP 41059/AA01
  - Investigation of Hermetic Sealing to Extend the Life of Film-Based Microfilm, July 31, 1997 - August 9, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    Contains a great deal of handwritten preliminary work.
  - Hermetic Sealing - 1, 1951 - September 3, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    The 1951 material are copies of correspondence with the US Treasury Department about Cornell's tax information. Most of the folder's other contents are from 2001.
  - Ford - Seal (Hermetic), June 1984 - October 14, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    Includes significantly older material because it contains a past study concerning hermetic sealing and microfilm storage.
  - Hermetic Sealing - 2, March 28, 2000 - February 4, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Hermetic Sealing - 3, June 26, 2001 - February 23, 2004 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Hermetic Sealing and Film-Based Material - Folder 1, September 3, 2001 - February 13, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Hermetic Sealing - 4, September 4, 2001 - September 12, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    Contains External Funding Proposal Impact and Approval Form.
  - Hermetic Sealing and Film-Based Material - Folder 2, November 15, 2001 - February 28, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Hermetic Sealing - 5, February 2002 - February 25, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    Includes proposal, award letter, and approved budget information.
  - Hermetic Sealing - 6, February 28, 2005 - January 9, 2006 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    Correspondences about the grant's possible extension and interm reports to the Ford Foundation.
  - Kenney, A. NEH Workshops and Online Tutorial, September 1, 2002 - December 31, 2004 (Box 132)
    NEH L61-8300; OSP 40781 - Workshops and an online tutorial on the preservation of digital resources.
  - NEH Workshops and Online Tutorial - Folder 1, June 21, 2001 - February 2, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - NEH Workshops and Online Tutorial - Folder 2, May 14, 2001 - June 2004 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - NEH Workshops and Online Tutorial - Folder 3, November 2, 2001 - March 31, 2005 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - McGovern, N. Political Communications Web Archiving, October 1, 2002 - December 31, 2003 (Box 133)
    CRL L61-8500; 43516/A001
  - CRL - Political Communications Web Archiving, July 26, 2002 - March 4, 2004 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Dean, J. Online Preservation Tutorial in Arabic, January 1, 2004 - December 31, 2005 (Box 133)
    NEH L89-8314; OSP 45351
  - Online Preservation Tutorial in Arabic, September 2003 - April 21, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Dean, J. IMLS Native American Libraries, September 1, 2004 - August 31, 2006 (Box 133)
    IMLS L89-8315; OSP 46225
  - IMLS Native American Libraries - Folder 1, March 22, 2002 - November 21, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - IMLS Native American Libraries - Folder 2, March 22, 2002 - July 13, 2004 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - IMLS Native American Libraries - Folder 3, January 3, 2003 - December 2004 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Kenney, A. Digital Preservation Management, January 1, 2005 - December 31, 2007 (Box 133)
    NEH L61-8301
  - Digital Preservation Management - Folder 1, June 2004 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Digital Preservation Management - Folder 2, June 2004 - January 14, 2005 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Digital Preservation Management - Folder 3, June 2004 - March 6, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - Digital Preservation Management - Folder 4, December 3, 2004 - July 15, 2008 (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - Kotas, Frederic J. Preserving and Enhancing Access to Maeda Ai Collection, May 1, 2005 - April 30, 2007 (Box 133)
  - Preserving and Enhancing Access to Maeda Ai Collection, 1992 - 2004 (Box 133, Folder 34)
  - Eden, Barbara B. Conservation Treatment of WWI and II Posters, July 1, 2005 - June 30, 2006 (Box 133)
    NEH L89-8044; OSP 486649
  - Conservation Treatment of WWI and II Posters, February 8, 2005 - January 25, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 35)
  - Dean, J. and Eden, B. Ethiopia Grant - State Department, July 1, 2005 - June 30, 2006 (Box 133)
    NYS The University of Addis Ababa and Cornell University: Respect for Cultural Property: The Conservation of Manuscripts
  - Ethiopia Grant - State Department, November 2004 (Box 133, Folder 36)
  - Dean, J. and Eden, B. The University of Addis Ababa and Cornell University Respect for Cultural Property - Conservation of Manuscripts, July 2005 - June 2006 (Box 133)
    CUL Department of State Bureau of Education and Cultural Affairs
  - The University of Addis Ababa and Cornell University Respect for Cultural Property - Conservation of Manuscripts, November 2004 (Box 133, Folder 37)
  - Hickerson, Thomas National Leadership Grant for Libraries: Preserving Art of the Future, November 1, 2005 - October 31, 2008 (Box 133)
  - National Leadership Grant for Libraries: Preserving Art of the Future, January 2005 (Box 133, Folder 38)
  - Engst, Elaine D.; Hickerston, Thomas H. Huntington Free Library Native American Collection Preservation Project, January 1, 2006 - December 31, 2009 (Box 133)
    NEH Save America's Treasures
  - Native American Collection - SAT Grant, January 10, 2005 - January 11, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 39)
  - Huntington Free Library Native American Collection Preservation Project, January 1, 2006 - December 31, 2009 (Box 133, Folder 40)
    In this case, the date given is the budget period, as the other material is undated.
  - Huntington Free Library Native American Collection Preservation Project; SAT; NEH, July 2005 - December 2006 (Box 133, Folder 41)
  - Eden, Barbara B. The Preservation Photocopying of New York State Historical Topographic Maps, July 1, 2006 - June 30, 2007 (Box 133)
    NYS L89-8049; OSP 51063; 0307-07-0003
  - The Preservation Photocopying of New York State Historical Topographic Maps, February 12, 2006 - November 2007 (Box 133, Folder 42)
  - Eden, Barbara B. A Training Program for Preservation of Works on Paper, July 1, 2006 - June 30, 2008 (Box 133)
    NYS L89-8054; OSP 51033
  - A Training Program for Preservation of Works on Paper - Folder 1, March 17, 2004 - May 15, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 43)
  - A Training Program for Preservation of Works on Paper - Folder 2, January 11, 2005 - May 7, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 44)
  - A Training Program for Preservation of Works on Paper - Folder 3, August 25, 2006 - November 14, 2008 (Box 133, Folder 45)
  - Works on Paper Year 2, November 7, 2006 - June 30, 2008 (Box 133, Folder 46)
  - Eden, Barbara B. The Andrew Dickson White Collection on the History of Witchcraft: the Need for Conservation, May 2008 - April 2010 (Box 133)
  - The Andrew Dickson White Collection on the History of Witchcraft: the Need for Conservation, March 1, 2007 - July 17, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 47)
  - Witch Photos, May 2007 (Box 133, Folder 48)
    Contains a CD and photos of various witchcraft books with brief descriptions.
  - Rieger, Oya Preservation and Access Framework for Digital Art Objects, January 2013 - February 2015 (Box 133)
  - Preservation and Access Framework for Digital Art Objects, May 2012 (Box 133, Folder 49)
    Contains grant application packet/proposal.